{"data":[{"question":"Nam is 1.7m tall. His brother is 1.4m tall. His brother is ________.","a":"short","b":"thin","c":"tall","d":"fat","answer":"1","explain":"\n- Short(adj): not tall\/ small in height","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"That book is not mine. It is ________, I think.","a":"her","b":"she","c":"hers","d":"your","answer":"3","explain":"\n- Hers: used as a possessive pronoun ( hers =her book)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Who is that? - It is ________.","a":"book","b":"Mr.Pike","c":"ruler","d":"me","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Who: used for asking which person is involved in something, so the answer would be person","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"What is the weather like today? It's ________ today.","a":"blue","b":"fine","c":"sad","d":"well","answer":"2","explain":"\n- If the weather is fine, it's sunny and not raining","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"How are you? I am ________, thanks.","a":"eleven","b":"big","c":"well","d":"sad","answer":"3","explain":"\n- If you are well, your health is good and you have no problems","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"My father is a doctor. Lan's father is a doctor, too. They are ________ doctors.","a":"not","b":"both","c":"or","d":"and","answer":"2","explain":"\n- Both: used when you are saying the same thing about two people or things","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"Oh, look at that cat. ________ is very nice ________ tail is very long and nice.","a":"It \/ It's","b":"It \/ Its","c":"It's \/ Its","d":"It \/ It","answer":"2","explain":"\n- That car: is an object- pronoun: it.\u00a0\n- My\/his\/her\/its\/our\/their: adjective pronoun: that modifies a noun by attributing possession (or other sense of belonging) to someone or something.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"This is our classroom, not Bob's. ________ classroom is over there. ________ isn't in the classroom now.","a":"His \/ He's","b":"His \/ His","c":"He's \/ His","d":"His \/ He","answer":"4","explain":"\n- I\/he\/she\/it\/we\/they: subject pronoun: play role as subject.\u00a0\n- My\/his\/her\/its\/our\/their: adjective pronoun: that modifies a noun by attributing possession (or other sense of belonging) to someone or something.\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"These are Bob and Boom. These books are not ________ . ________ are in the desk.","a":"their \/ Theirs","b":"theirs \/ Them","c":"theirs \/ Their","d":"theirs \/ Theirs","answer":"4","explain":"\n- Theirs: used as a possessive pronoun followed by a noun (theirs = Bob and Boom's books)","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"},{"question":"________ house is big but ________ is small.","a":"Our \/ Theirs","b":"Ours \/ Their","c":"Our \/ Their","d":"Ours \/ Theirs","answer":"1","explain":"- Our: used as a adjective determiner followed by a noun\u00a0\n- Theirs: used as a \u00a0possessive pronoun followed by a verb\u00a0","category":"3","subcategorylv1":"17","subcategorylv2":"8","type":"1"}]}